Guide to the Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
Comic book collection
- Enigma, 1993; 8 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1988; 1 (Box 9)
  Author: Chris Claremont
- Excalibur, 1988; 2 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1988; 3 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1988; 4 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 5 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 6 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 7 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 8 (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Ron Lim
- Excalibur, 1989; 9 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 10 (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Marshall Rogers
- Excalibur, 1989; 11 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 12 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 13 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 14 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 15 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 16 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1989; 17 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1990; 18 (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Dennis Jensen
- Excalibur, 1990; 19 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1990; 20 (Box 9)
  Author: Michael Higgins
- Excalibur, 1990; 21 (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Chris Wozniak
- Excalibur, 1990; 22 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1990; 23 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1990; 24 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1990; 25 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1990; 26 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1990; 27 (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Barry Windsor-Smith
- Excalibur, 1990; 28 (Box 9)
  Author: Terry Austin
  Artist/Penciler: Colleen Doran
- Excalibur, 1990; 29 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1990; 30 (Box 9)
  Author: Dana Moreshead
- Excalibur, 1990; 31 (Box 9)
  Author: Scott Lobdel
- Excalibur, 1991; 32 (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Ron Wagner
- Excalibur, 1991; 33 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1991; 41 (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Dave Hoover
- Excalibur, 1991; 42 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1991; 43 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1991; 44 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 45 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 46 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 47 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 48 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 49 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 50 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 51 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 52 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 53 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 54 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 55 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 56 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 57 (Box 9)
  Author: Alan Davis, Scott Lobdel
  Artist/Penciler: Joe Madureira
- Excalibur, 1992; 58 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1992; 59 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 60 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 61 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 62 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 63 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 64 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 65 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 66 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 67 (Box 9)
- Excalibur, 1993; 68 (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Buccellato
- Excalibur: The Possession, 1991; — (Box 9)
  Artist/Penciler: Tom Morgan
- Excalibur: XX Crossing, 1992; — (Box 9)
  Notes: Cover title: "Excalibur Special Edition"
- Exciting X-Patrol, 1997; 1 (Box 9)
  Author: Barbara Kesel
- Exquisite Corpse, 1990; Yellow (Box 9)
  Notes: Issues have colors instead of numbers
- Extremist, The, 1993; 1 (Box 9)
- Extremist, The, 1993; 2 (Box 9)
- Extremist, The, 1993; 3 (Box 9)
- Extremist, The, 1993; 4 (Box 9)
- Fables, 2002; 1 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Lan Medina
- Fables, 2002; 2 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2002; 3 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2002; 4 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2002; 5 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2002; 6 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 7 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 8 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 9 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 10 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 11 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Bryan Talbot
- Fables, 2003; 12 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 13 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 14 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 15 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 17 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2003; 18 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 19 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 20 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 21 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 22 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Tony Akins
- Fables, 2004; 23 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 24 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 25 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 26 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 27 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 28 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 29 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2004; 30 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2005; 31 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2005; 32 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2005; 33 (Box 10)
- Fables, 2005; 34 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: David Hahn
- Fables, 2005; 35 (Box 10)
- Face, 1995; 1 (Box 10)
- Faith, 1999; 1 (Box 10)
- Faith, 1999; 2 (Box 10)
- Faith, 2000; 3 (Box 10)
- Faith, 2000; 4 (Box 10)
- Falcon, The, 1983; 1 (Box 10)
  Author: Jim Owsley
  Notes: four issue limited series
- Falcon, The, 1983; 2 (Box 10)
- Falcon, The, 1983; 3 (Box 10)
- Falcon, The, 1983; 4 (Box 10)
- Fall, The, 2001 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Jason Lutes
  Publisher: Drawn and Quarterly
- Fallen Angels, 1987; 1 (Box 10)
  Author: Jo Duffy
  Artist/Penciler: Kerry Gammill
  Notes: eight issue limited series
- Fantastic Four, 1967; 66 (Box 10)
- Fantastic Four, 1967; 67 (Box 10)
- Fantastic Four (v.3), 1998; 1 (Box 10)
- Fantastic Four (v.3), 1998; 2 (Box 10)
- Farscape: War Torn, 2002; 1 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Robert Teranishi
- Fast Forward, 1992; 1 (Box 10)
  Publisher: Piranha Press
  Notes: compilation
- Fast Forward, 1992; 2 (Box 10)
  Author: Kyle Baker
- Fast Forward, 1992; 3 (Box 10)
  Author: Steve Purcell
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Purcell
- Fate, 1995; 8 (Box 10)
  Author: Steve Grant
  Artist/Penciler: Len Kaminski
- Faultlines, 1997; 1 (Box 10)
  Author: Lee Marrs
  Artist/Penciler: Bill Koeb
- Faultlines, 1997; 2 (Box 10)
- Faultlines, 1997; 3 (Box 10)
- Faultlines, 1997; 4 (Box 10)
- Faultlines, 1997; 5 (Box 10)
- Fight Man, 1993; 1 (Box 10)
- Filth, The, 2002; 1 (Box 10)
  Notes: thirteen issue limited series
- Filth, The, 2002; 2 (Box 10)
- Filth, The, 2002; 3 (Box 10)
- Filth, The, 2002; 4 (Box 10)
- Filth, The, 2002; 5 (Box 10)
- Final Night, 1996; 1 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Stuart Immonen
- Final Night, 1996; 2 (Box 10)
- Final Night, 1996; 3 (Box 10)
- Final Night, 1996; 4 (Box 10)
- Finals, 1999; 1 (Box 10)
  Author: Will Pfeifer
- Finder, 1999; 15 (Box 10)
  Author: Carla Speed McNeil
  Artist/Penciler: Carla Speed McNeil
  Publisher: Lightspeed
- Finder, 2000; 16 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2000; 17 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2000; 18 (Box 10)
- Finder, 1999; 19 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2000; 20 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2001; 21 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2001; 22 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2001; 23 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2001; 24 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2002; 25 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2002; 26 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2002; 27 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2002; 28 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2002; 29 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2003; 30 (Box 10)
- Finder, 2003; 31 (Box 10)
- Firestorm (v.2), 2004; 1 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Chris Cross
- Firestorm (v.2), 2004; 2 (Box 10)
- Firestorm (v.2), 2004; 3 (Box 10)
- Firestorm (v.2), 2004; 4 (Box 10)
- Firestorm (v.2), 2004; 5 (Box 10)
- Firestorm (v.2), 2004; 6 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Chris Batista
- Firestorm (v.2), 2005; 7 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Liam Sharp
- Firestorm (v.2), 2005; 8 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Jamal Igle
- Firestorm (v.2), 2005; 9 (Box 10)
- Firestorm (v.2), 2005; 10 (Box 10)
- Firestorm (v.2), 2005; 11 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Dale Eaglesham
- Fish Police (v.1), 1986; 1 (Box 10)
  Author: Steven Moncuse
  Artist/Penciler: Steven Moncuse
  Publisher: Fishwrap
- Fish Police (v.1), 1986; 3 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1986; 4 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1986; 5 (Box 10)
  Publisher:
- Fish Police (v.1), 1986; 6 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1987; 7 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1987; 8 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1987; 9 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1987; 10 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1987; 11 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1988; 12 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1988; 13 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1988; 14 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1989; 15 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1989; 16 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1989; 17 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1989; 18 (Box 10)
  Publisher: Apple
- Fish Police (v.1), 1989; 19 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1990; 20 (Box 10)
- Fish Police (v.1), 1999; 21 (Box 10)
- Fish Police Color Special, 1987; 1 (Box 10)
- Flaming Carrot Comics, 1988; 20 (Box 10)
  Author: Bob Burden
  Artist/Penciler: Bob Burden
- Flaming Carrot Comics, 1989; 21 (Box 10)
- Flaming Carrot Comics, 1989; 22 (Box 10)
- Flaming Carrot Comics, 1989; 23 (Box 10)
- Flaming Carrot Comics, 1989; 24 (Box 10)
- Flaming Carrot Comics, 1989; 25 (Box 10)
- Flaming Carrot Comics, 1989; 26 (Box 10)
- Flash, The (v.2), 1996; 110 (Box 10)
  Author: Mark Waid
  Artist/Penciler: Oscar Jimenez
- Flash, The (v.2), 1996; 111 (Box 10)
- Flash, The (v.2), 1996; 112 (Box 10)
- Foot Soldiers (v.2), 1997; 1 (Box 10)
  Author: Jim Kruger
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Yeowell, Phil Hester
- Foot Soldiers (v.2), 1997; 2 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: Phil Hester
- Formerly Known as the Justice League, 2003; 1 (Box 10)
  Artist/Penciler: J.M. DeMatteis
- Formerly Known as the Justice League, 2 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1994; 1 (Box 10)
  Publisher: Top Shelf
  Notes: 3rd printing
- From Hell, 1994; 2 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1993; 3 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1994; 4 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1994; 5 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1994; 6 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1995; 7 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1995; 8 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1996; 9 (Box 10)
- From Hell, 1996; 10 (Box 10)
- From Hell: Dance of the Gull-Catchers, 1998 (Box 10)
  Notes: Epilogue
- Fugitoid, 1985; 1 (Box 10)
  Notes: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles spin-off; irregular-size, on side of box. 2 copies.
- Futurians (v.1), 1985; 1 (Box 10)
  Author: Dave Cockrum
  Artist/Penciler: Dave Cockrum
  Publisher: Lodestone
- Futurians (v.1), 1985; 2 (Box 10)
- Futurians (v.1), 1985; 3 (Box 10)
- Futurians (v.2), 1995; 0 (Box 10)
  Publisher: Aardwolf
- Gary Gianni's The Monstermen, 1999 (Box 11)
  Author: Gary Gianni
  Artist/Penciler: Gary Gianni
- Geisha, 1998; 1 (Box 11)
- Geisha, 1998; 2 (Box 11)
- Geisha, 1998; 3 (Box 11)
- Geisha, 1998; 4 (Box 11)
- Gen13, 1996; 13B (Box 11)
  Author: Brandon Choi
  Artist/Penciler: J. Scott Campbell
- Gen13: Ordinary heroes, 1996; 1 (Box 11)
  Author: Adam Hughes
  Artist/Penciler: Adam Hughes
- Gen13: Ordinary heroes, 1996; 2 (Box 11)
- Generation Next, 1995; 1 (Box 11)
  Notes: Miniseries in "Age of Apocalypse" crossover, published between Generation X #4 & #5.
- Generation Next, 1995; 2 (Box 11)
- Generation Next, 1995; 3 (Box 11)
- Generation Next, 1995; 4 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1994; 1 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1994; 2 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; 3 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; 4 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; 5 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; 6 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; 7 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Rober Cruz
- Generation X, 1995; 8 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; 9 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; 10 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Pascual Ferry
- Generation X, 1996; 11 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1996; 12 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; 13 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1996; 17 (Box 11)
  Author: Scott Lobdel, Stan Lee
- Generation X, 1996; 18 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1996; 19 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1996; 20 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1996; 21 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1996; 22 (Box 11)
- Generation X, 1995; Ann. '95 (Box 11)
  Author: Scott Lobdel, Jeph Loeb
  Artist/Penciler: Wallace Wood, Shawn McManus
- Generation X, 1996; Ann. '96 (Box 11)
  Author: Michael Golden
  Artist/Penciler: Jeff Johnson
- Generic Comic Book, 1984; 1 (Box 11)
  Author: Steve Skeates
  Artist/Penciler: Larry Hama
- Genesis, 1997; 1 (Box 11)
  Notes: DC event miniseries
- Genesis, 1997; 2 (Box 11)
- Genesis, 1997; 3 (Box 11)
- Genesis, 1997; 4 (Box 11)
- Ghost (v.1), 1995; 1 (Box 11)
  Author: Eric Luke
- Ghost (v.1), 1995; 2 (Box 11)
- Ghost (v.1), 1995; 3 (Box 11)
- Ghost (v.1), 1995; 4 (Box 11)
- Ghost (v.1), 1995; 5 (Box 11)
- Ghost (v.1), 1996; 6 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Scott Benefiel
- Ghost (v.1), 1996; 7 (Box 11)
- Ghost (v.1), 1996; 8 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Geroge Dove
- Ghost (v.1), 1996; 9 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: H.M. Baker
- Ghost (v.1), 1996; 10 (Box 11)
- Ghost (v.1), 1996; 12 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: David Bolluck
- Ghost and the Shadow, 1995 (Box 11)
- Ghost Rider, 1992; 26 (Box 11)
  Author: Howard Mackie
  Notes: X-Men cross-over
- Ghost Ship, 1996; 1 (Box 11)
  Author: Jon Lewis
  Artist/Penciler: Jon Lewis
- Ghost Ship, 1996; 2 (Box 11)
- Ghost Ship, 1996; 3 (Box 11)
- Ghost Special, 1994; 1 (Box 11)
- Ghost/Hellboy, 1995; 1 (Box 11)
- Ghost/Hellboy, 1995; 2 (Box 11)
- Ghostdancing, 1995; 1 (Box 11)
  Notes: six issue limited-series
- Ghostdancing, 1995; 2 (Box 11)
- Ghostdancing, 1995; 3 (Box 11)
- Ghostdancing, 1995; 4 (Box 11)
- Ghostdancing, 1995; 5 (Box 11)
- Ghostdancing, 1995; 6 (Box 11)
- Giantkiller, 1999; 1 (Box 11)
  Author: Dan Bereton
  Artist/Penciler: Dan Bereton
- Giantkiller, 1999; 2 (Box 11)
- Giantkiller, 1999; 3 (Box 11)
- Gifts of the Night, 1999; 1 (Box 11)
- Gifts of the Night, 1999; 2 (Box 11)
- Gifts of the Night, 1999; 3 (Box 11)
- Gifts of the Night, 1999; 4 (Box 11)
- Girl, 1996; 1 (Box 11)
- Girl, 1996; 2 (Box 11)
- Girl, 1996; 3 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2000; 0 (Box 11)
  Author: Phil Foglio
  Artist/Penciler: Phil Foglio
  Publisher: Airship
  Notes: Cover title: "Girl Genius: Secret Blueprints for Volume One"
- Girl Genius, 2001; 1 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 2 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 3 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 4 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 5 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 6 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 7 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 8 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 9 (Box 11)
- Girl Genius, 2001; 10 (Box 11)
- Girl Who Would be Death, The, 1998; 1 (Box 11)
- Girl Who Would be Death, The, 1998; 2 (Box 11)
- Girl Who Would be Death, The, 1998; 3 (Box 11)
- Girl Who Would be Death, The, 1998; 4 (Box 11)
- Global Frequency, 2001; 1 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Gary Leach
  Notes: twelve part limited series
- Global Frequency, 2002; 2 (Box 11)
- Global Frequency, 2002; 3 (Box 11)
- Global Frequency, 2002; 4 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Roy A. Martinez
- Global Frequency, 2002; 5 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: John J. Muth
- Global Frequency, 2002; 6 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: David Lloyd
- Global Frequency, 2002; 7 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Simon Bisley
- Global Frequency, 2002; 8 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Chris Sprouse
- Global Frequency, 2002; 9 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Lee Bermejo
- Global Frequency, 2002; 10 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Tomm Coker
- Global Frequency, 2002; 11 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Jason Pearson
- Global Frequency, 2002; 12 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Gene Ha
- Goddess, 1995; 1 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Phil Winslade
- Goddess, 1995; 2 (Box 11)
- Goddess, 1995; 3 (Box 11)
- Goddess, 1995; 4 (Box 11)
- Goddess, 1995; 5 (Box 11)
- Goddess, 1995; 6 (Box 11)
- Goddess, 1995; 7 (Box 11)
- Goddess, 1996; 8 (Box 11)
- Gods and Tulips, 1993 (Box 11)
  Publisher: Westhampton
  Notes: CBLDF fundraiser
- Golden Age, The, 1995; TPB (Box 11)
- Good Guys, The, 1993; 1 (Box 11)
  Author: Jim Shooter
  Artist/Penciler: Janet Jackson
- Good Guys, The, 1993; 2 (Box 11)
- Good Guys, The, 1993; 3 (Box 11)
- Good Guys, The, 1993; 4 (Box 11)
- Good Guys, The, 1993; 5 (Box 11)
- Good Guys, The, 1993; 6 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2001; 1 (Box 11)
  Author: Kevin Smith
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2001; 2 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2001; 3 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2001; 4 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2001; 5 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2001; 7 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2001; 8 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2001; 9 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2002; 10 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2002; 11 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2002; 12 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2002; 13 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2002; 14 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2002; 15 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2002; 16 (Box 11)
  Author: Brad Meltzer
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2002; 17 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 18 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 19 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 20 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 21 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 22 (Box 11)
  Author: Scott Beatty
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 23 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 24 (Box 11)
  Author: Ben Raab
  Artist/Penciler: Ben Adlard
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 25 (Box 11)
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 26 (Box 11)
  Author: Judd Winick
- Green Arrow (v.3), 2003; 27 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 1998; 98 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Darryl Banks
- Green Lantern (v.3), 1998; 99 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2002; 154 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2002; 155 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2003; 158 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2003; 159 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2003; 160 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2003; 161 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2003; 162 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2003; 163 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2003; 164 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern (v.3), 2003; 166 (Box 11)
- Green Lantern/Superman: Legend of the green flame, 2000 (Box 11)
  Notes: various artists
- Green Lantern: 1001 Emerald Nights, 2001; — (Box 11)
  Author: Terry Laban
- Green Lantern: Rebirth, 2004; 1 (Box 11)
  Artist/Penciler: Ethan van Sciver
- Gregory IV: Fat Boy, 1993 (Box 11)
  Author: Marc Hempel
- Grendel (v.2), 1986; 1 (Box 12)
  Artist/Penciler: Matt Wagner
  Notes: Issues 1-12: Devil's Legacy. 2 copies
- Grendel (v.2), 1986; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1986; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 4 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 5 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 6 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 7 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 8 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 9 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 10 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 11 (Box 12)
  Artist/Penciler: Pander Bros.
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 12 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 13 (Box 12)
  Artist/Penciler: Bernie Mireault
  Notes: Issues 16-19: Devil Tracks and Devil Eyes
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 14 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1987; 15 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 16 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 17 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 18 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 19 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 20 (Box 12)
  Artist/Penciler: Hannibal King
  Notes: Issues 20-23: The Incubation Years
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 21 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 22 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 23 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 24 (Box 12)
  Notes: Issues 24-33: God and the Devil
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 25 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 26 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1988; 27 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 28 (Box 12)
  Artist/Penciler: John K. Synder III
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 29 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 30 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 31 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 32 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 33 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 34 (Box 12)
  Notes: Issues 34-40: Devil's Reign
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 35 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 36 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 37 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 38 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1989; 39 (Box 12)
- Grendel (v.2), 1990; 40 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Devils and Deaths, 1994; 1 (Box 12)
  Author: Darko Macan
  Artist/Penciler: Edvin Biukovic
- Grendel Tales: Devils and Deaths, 1994; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Devil's choices, 1995; 1 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Devil's choices, 1995; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Devil's choices, 1995; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Devil's choices, 1995; 4 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Devil's hammer, 1994; 1 (Box 12)
  Author: Rob Walton
  Artist/Penciler: Rob Walton
- Grendel Tales: Devil's hammer, 1994; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Devil's hammer, 1994; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Four devils, one hell, 1993; 1 (Box 12)
  Artist/Penciler: Teddy Kristiansen
- Grendel Tales: Four devils, one hell, 1993; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Four devils, one hell, 1993; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Four devils, one hell, 1993; 4 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Four devils, one hell, 1993; 5 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Four devils, one hell, 1993; 6 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Homecoming, 1994; 1 (Box 12)
  Author: Patrick McEown
  Artist/Penciler: Patrick McEown
- Grendel Tales: Homecoming, 1994; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: Homecoming, 1994; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil in our midst, 1994; 1 (Box 12)
  Author: Steven T. Seagle
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Girst
- Grendel Tales: The devil in our midst, 1994; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil in our midst, 1994; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil in our midst, 1994; 4 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil in our midst, 1994; 5 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil may care, 1995; 1 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil may care, 1995; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil may care, 1995; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil may care, 1995; 4 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil may care, 1995; 5 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil may care, 1995; 6 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil's apprentice, 1997; 1 (Box 12)
  Author: Jerry Lang
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Lieber
- Grendel Tales: The devil's apprentice, 1997; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel Tales: The devil's apprentice, 1997; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel: Black white & red, 1998; 1 (Box 12)
  Notes: various artists featuring Tim Sale, D'Israeli, John Paul Leon, Duncan Fegredo, Ho Che Anderson
- Grendel: Black white & red, 1998; 2 (Box 12)
  Notes: various artists featuring Bernie Mireault, David Mack, Tim Bradstreet, C. Scott Morse, Paul Chadwick
- Grendel: Black white & red, 1998; 3 (Box 12)
  Notes: various artists featuring Mike Allred, Pander Bros., Stan Shaw, Teddy Kristiansen, Guy Davis
- Grendel: Black white & red, 1998; 4 (Box 12)
  Notes: various artists featuring Jason Pearson Woodrow Pheonix, Chris Sprouse, Jason Martin, Jay Geldhof Try Nixey
- Grendel: Devil child, 1998; 1 (Box 12)
  Artist/Penciler: Diana Schutz
- Grendel: Devil child, 1998; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel: Red, white, & black, 2002; 1 (Box 12)
  Notes: various artists featuring Jill Thompson, Andy Kuhn, Stan Sakai, Jim Mahfood, Tom fowler
- Grendel: War Child, 1992; 1 (Box 12)
  Notes: Issues 41-50: War Child continue ongoing series
- Grendel: War Child, 1992; 2 (Box 12)
- Grendel: War Child, 1992; 3 (Box 12)
- Grendel: War Child, 1992; 4 (Box 12)
- Grendel: War Child, 1992; 5 (Box 12)
- Grendel: War Child, 1992; 6 (Box 12)
- Grendel: War Child, 1993; 7 (Box 12)
- Grendel: War Child, 1993; 8 (Box 12)
- Grendel: War Child, 1993; 9 (Box 12)
- Grendel: War Child, 1993; 10 (Box 12)
- Gumby's Winter Fun Special, 1988; 1 (Box 12)
- Guy Gardner: Warrior, 1995; 29 (Box 12)
  Author: Beau Smith
  Artist/Penciler: Phil Jimenez
- Hands Off!, 1994 (Box 12)
  Notes: antiviolence benefit
- Hardware, 1993; 1 (Box 12)
- Hardware, 1995; 29 (Box 12)
  Author: Dewayne McDuffie
  Artist/Penciler: Humberto Ramos
- Harlan Ellison's Dream Corridor, 1995; 1 (Box 12)
  Artist/Penciler: Eric Shanower
- Harlan Ellison's Dream Corridor, 1995; 2 (Box 12)
- Harlan Ellison's Dream Corridor, 1995; 3 (Box 12)
- Harlan Ellison's Dream Corridor, 1995; 4 (Box 12)
- Harlan Ellison's Dream Corridor, 1995; 5 (Box 12)
- Harlan Ellison's Dream Corridor Quarterly, 1995; 1 (Box 12)
- Harlan Ellison's Dream Corridor Special, 2005 (Box 12)
- Haven: The Broken City, 2002; 1 (Box 12)
  Author: Ashley-Jane Nicolaus, Matthew P. Schuster
  Artist/Penciler: Ariel Olivetti
- Haven: The Broken City, 2002; 2 (Box 12)
- Haven: The Broken City, 2002; 3 (Box 12)
- Haven: The Broken City, 2002; 4 (Box 12)
- Haven: The Broken City, 2002; 5 (Box 12)
- Hawkeye, 1983; 1 (Box 12)
  Author: Mark Gruenwald
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Gruenwald
- Hawkeye, 1983; 2 (Box 12)
- Hawkeye, 1983; 3 (Box 12)
- Hawkeye, 1983; 4 (Box 12)
- Heartland, 1997 (Box 12)
- Heartthrobs, 1999; 1 (Box 12)
  Notes: four issue limited series featuring Brian Bolland, Robert Rodi and Phil Jimenez, Steve T. Seagle and Time Sale
- Heartthrobs, 1999; 2 (Box 12)
  Notes: featuring Brian Azzarello and Tim Bradstreet, Ilya and Frank Quitely, Doselle Young and Tony Salmons
- Heartthrobs, 1999; 3 (Box 12)
  Notes: featuring Richard Corbern and Simon Revelstroke, Peter Milligan and Eduardo Risso, Marguerite Van Cook and James Romberger
- Heartthrobs, 1999; 4 (Box 12)
  Notes: featuring Bob Fingerman and Pat McEown, Steve Gerber and Danijel Zezelj, Scott Cunninghma and Miran Kim
- Heavy Liquid, 1999; 1 (Box 12)
  Notes: five issue limited series
- Heavy Liquid, 1999; 2 (Box 12)
- Heavy Liquid, 1999; 3 (Box 12)
- Heavy Liquid, 2000; 4 (Box 12)
- Heavy Liquid, 2000; 5 (Box 12)
- Heckler, 1992; 1 (Box 12)
- Heckler, 1992; 2 (Box 12)